American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File
1831-1943
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Association for Labor Legislation
5001 PAM
19 cubic feet
19 linear ft.
Pamphlets.
8439351
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 24, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The American Association for Labor Legislation was formed to promote uniformity of labor legislation and to encourage the study of labor conditions with a view toward promoting desirable legislation.
The Association was founded as a branch of the International Association for Labor Legislation. Preliminary discussions about forming the group occurred during 1905 and culminated in the first meeting of the Association held on February 15, 1906, in New York City.
During the Association's first few years, three basic objectives were established: to serve as the American branch of the International Association for Labor Legislation; to promote uniformity of labor legislation in the United States; and to encourage the study of labor conditions with a view toward promoting desirable labor legislation.
John Bertram Andrews was appointed executive secretary in 1909. His wife, Irene Osgood Andrews, eventually became associate secretary. John Andrews, as lobbyist, lecturer, author and editor of the publication THE AMERICAN LABOR LEGISLATION REVIEW, became the motivating force of the Association. Broadly speaking, the American Association for Labor Legislation set the following goals: the alleviation of adverse working conditions; the creation of laws to protect safety and health on the job; and the provision of compensation in times of unemployment and benefits for workers no longer able to participate in the labor force. To facilitate the implementation of the Association's interests, study groups were established to investigate labor conditions. Active lobbying was undertaken in support of protective labor legislation in state and federal legislatures, and critiques were published concerning pending bills. The lifetime of the Association roughly corresponded to Andrew's lifetime; its activities ceased after his death in 1943.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5001: American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001 mf: American Association for Labor Legislation Records on Microfilm 5002: American Association for Social Security Records
American Association for Labor Legislation
8439351
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Rules, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Constitution and Rules, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Current Activities of the American Construction Council, 1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Interim Report of the Building Resettlement Committee on the Supply of Building Labour for the Government Housing Schemes, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: First Report of the Safety and Welfare Committee appointed by The Building Trade Joint Industrial Council, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Supplementary Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Report of Proceedings of the Inaugural Meeting held at The Central Hall, Westminster, London, S.W.I on Wednesday and Thursday, May 29th and 30th, 1918, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Resolution, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Standing Committees of The American Construction Council, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: If My Child-, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Compulsory Continuation Schools The Massachusetts Plan, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Child Labor Laws of Massachusetts (1910.), Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Hours for Children, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The Duplex Envelope Co., Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Separate Courts of Justice for Children. Probation & Probation Officers, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Child Labor Inspection Insurance and Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Report of the Kansas Children's Code Commission, 1921; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: "War Against Poverty" The New Children's Charter By C.M. Lloyd, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Legal Notice., 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Child Labor Law, 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Laws Pertaining to the Employment of Women and Children, 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: The Economics of Child Welfare, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: The Girl Employed in Hotels and Restaurants, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Children in War Time Second Article: Child Labor in Warring Countries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Children in War Time First Article: Child Labor on English Farms, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Children in War Time Third Article: How Canada Takes Cares of Soldiers' Children, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Summary of Address on Child Labor and Public Health, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Owen R. Lovejoy
    Format: Publication
  - Item 19: 20 Questions About Going to Work, 1921; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: 20 Questions About Going to Work, 1921; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: National Child Labor Committee Ninth Annual Conference "Child Labor and Poverty", 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: To Women and Girls who work in Massachusetts, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Brief Outline of Laws Relating to Employment of Women and Children, 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Seattle Children in School and in Industry, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Anna Y. Reed
  - Item 25: Home Work in Tenements, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Home Work in Tenements, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the Rhode Island Children's Laws Commission, 1926; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Child Labor on the Stage in San Francisco, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Education Committee, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Education Committee, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Memorandum on "Trends" Graphically Plotted in Ratio of National Child Labor Committee, 1926; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Edward W. Macy
  - Item 6: An Amendment to the Constitution is Needed to Give The United States Power to Safeguard The Child Life of the Nation, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Laws Relating to Employment and Deportment of Children, 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: State Child-Labor Standards, January 1, 1926, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Child Labor Work of the League, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Weekly News Letter, 1926; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Child Welfare Commission Bills, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Laws Relating to Child Labour in Canada, 1926; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Ohio Laws Affecting the Employment of Women and Minors, 1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Monthly News Letter, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The League Bulletin, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The American Child, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Summary of the Conclusions of the Conference on Present Day Child Labor Problems, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Report on Child Labor in Agricultire in Colorado made to the Committee on Vocational Guidance of the Colorado White House Conference on Child Health and Protection, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: John Gross
  - Item 7: Education and Child Labor in the Southern States, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Legislative Activities, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Newsboys of New York, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Harry M. Shulman
  - Item 10: A Study of Industrial Injuries To Working Childing In Cincinnati During 1926, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: News, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: "My Dear. Mr. President, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Elmer F. Andrews
  - Item 3: Good Child-Labor Legislation Promotes the Health and Welfare of Children, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Good Child-Labor Legislations Promotes the Health and Welfare of Children, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: "Children Preferred" A Study of Child Labor in Pennsylvania, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Child Labor in Wisconsin 1917-1935, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Child Labor Amendment, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: William D. Guthrie
  - Item 2: The Challenge of Childhood To Louisiana, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Sunday News, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Caddies of Erie County N.Y., 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The Importance of Ratifying the Federal Child Labor Amendment, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Robert F. Wagner
  - Item 6: Ratify the Child Labor Amendment, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Ratify the Child Labor Amendment, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Child Labor Amendment Argument for Ratification, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: In Answer to the American Bar Association Committee on the Federal Child Labor Amendment, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Excerpt from Child Labor Amendment Argument for Ratification, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Excerpt from Child Labor Amendment Argument for Ratification, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Congressional Record, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Edward P. Costigan
  - Item 13: Congressional Record, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Changes Suggested for Standard Child Labor Law, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Answer to President Butler's Criticisim of the Proposed Child Labor Amendment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: William Draper Lewis
- Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Please Return This Little Book in the Enclosed Envelope, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Laws Under the Adminisration of the State Child Welfare Commission, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: A Study of Cincinnati's "Amateur Night" children By the Juvenile Protective Association of Cincinnati, 1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Concurrent Resolution Urging the Congress of the United States to Adopt A Constitutional Amendment Conferring Upon The Congress Power to Prohibit or Limit Child Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Mr. Antin
  - Item 5: A Picture of Small Industry in Lower Manhattan, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Re-educating the Jobless Child, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Miriam Keeler
  - Item 7: News, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Children's Department Life Extension Institute, Inc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Children's Department Life Extension Institute, Inc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Frances L. Campbell; Complainent, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Instructions to Physicians for Filling in Records of Physical Examinations of Children Applying for Employment Certificates, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Budget of the National Child Labor Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: How The Child Labor Bill (A-174) Would Affect Farmers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: What Boys and Girls in New Jersey May Do Under The New 1940 State Child Labor Laws (Effective September 1, 1940), Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: James E. Sidel
  - Item 15: Legislative Activities, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Twenty-Eighth Annual Luncheon of the National Child Labor Committee, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Twenty-Eighth Annual Luncheon of the National Child Labor Committee, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Who's Who on Our Board of Trustees, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: The Twelfth Annual Conference, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Child Labor, 1904-1912 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Report to Members, 1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Judiciary Committee Members Who Voted Against Reporting Child Labor Amendment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Summary of Present Child-Labor Problems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: City Churches in Social Action; The Social Activities of the Los Angeles Federation of Churches, 1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: James Myers
  - Item 2: Christian Unity To What extent is it Possible? What Actual forms Should it Take?, 1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Special Meeting of the Commission on the Church and Social Service, 1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: H.S. Braucher
  - Item 4: Report on American Coopeartion with the International Christian Social Institute and Bureau of Research, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Worth M. Tippy
  - Item 5: American Friends Service Committee, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Church and Society, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Brief to the American Friends' Service Committee From James Myers, Industrial Secretary, Federal Council of Churches, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: J. Howard Branson
  - Item 8: Committee on Social Legislation, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Minutes of the Meeting of the National Social Work Council, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Josiah Strong Memorial, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Josiah Strong Memorial, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Report of the Committee on Social Ideals of the Churches, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Charles N. Lathrop
  - Item 13: Central Church Methodist Episcopal Brooklyn, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Its Scope and Activities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Winter Meeting, Y.W.C.A., 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: A Summary of the Treasurer's Report, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Information Service, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Free Synagogue Carnegie Hall, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Stephen S. Wise
  - Item 19: Quadrennial and Twientieth Aniversary December 5-12, 1928 at Rochester, New york, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Outline of the Work of James Myers, 1928; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: September 30, 1932 Meeting; Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Labor Pagaent, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Second Draft of Labor Sunday Message, 1932, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Suggested Outline on Christianity And Industrial Problems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: No 1 Statement of Aims and Principles, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: John J. Mahoney
  - Item 2: Brill News, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Spring Festival and Ball, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Preliminary Announcement of the Second Annual Session of the Institute of Statesmanship, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Case of Charlotte Anita Whitney, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Franklin Hichborn
  - Item 2: To the American People: Report Upon the Illegal Practices of the United States Department of Justice, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: "Our Buddie" Sergt. "Bill" Cunnigham, 1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: In the United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: For Defense of the Schools -- A United Teachers Union, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Bulletin No. 2, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Bulletin No. 6, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Bulletin No. 7, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Bulletin No. 10, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Bulletin No. 11, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Bulletin No. 8, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Bulletin No. 9, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Bulletin No. 5, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Bulletin No. 4, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Bulletin No. 1, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Bulletin No. 3, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Draft of Report of the Council, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Examinations for the State, County, and Village Service, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Selection of Assisstant Commissioner of Labor Statistics, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Monseigneur a Petition, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: J.A. Whalen
  - Item 16: Chairman Transit Report, 1921; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: William F. Howes
  - Item 17: Tenth annual Convention, 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Mr. Lake
  - Item 18: Detail of Estimated General Expenditures for 1927, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Tentative Program Seventeenth Annual Convention, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Eraminations for the State, County, and Village Service, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Twelth Annual Convention, 1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Annual Meetings of Executives of Public Welfare, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Educational Program, 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Bribe Taker and Bribe Giver, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Edward T. Devine
  - Item 2: The Illinois Crime Survey, 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Bulletin No. 22, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Box: 1, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Decisions under the Employers' Liability Act, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: William H. Hoxie
  - Item 2: Decisions Under the Safety Appliance Acts Automatic Couplers, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Decisions Under the Safety Appliance Acts Automatic Couplers, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: In the Supreme Court of the State of Kansas, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Court of Appeals State of New York, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Minneapolis St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie Railway Company, vs. Railroad Commission of Wisconsin, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Frank Vasala vs Carpenter, Boxley & Herrick, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: In the Supreme Court of Errors, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Edward G. Mondou
  - Item 9: The Missouri Pacific Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error, v Henry Brinkmeier, Defendant in Error, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: The Missouri Pacific Railway Company, Plaintiff in Error, v. Henry Brinkmeier, Defendant in Error, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: St. Louis, Iron Mountain and Southern Railway Company v. Taylor, Administratrix, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Earl Ives -against- The South Buffalo Railway Company, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Pound J
- Box: 1, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Edward G. Borgnis Et Al., vs. The Falk Company, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Court of Appeals State of New York, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: State of Washington vs. Henrietta Somerville, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The People of The State, Defendant in Error, vs. Edward H. Elerding, Plaintiff in Error., 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Justice Vickers
  - Item 5: Appendix 2, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: The Court of Appeals of the State of New York, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Opinion of the Supreme Court of the State of Washington, Sustaining the Compulsory, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Box: 1, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The State of Washington vs Henrietta Somerville, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: State of Washington, ex rel. Davis-Smith Co., vs. C.W. Clausen, as State Auditor of the State of Washington, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: State of Wisconsin in Supreme Court, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: In the Matter of the Application of F.A. Miller, For a Writ of Habeas Corpus., 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: John B. Andrews
- Box: 1, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: State of Missouri ex re. Henry J. Westhues, Proscuting Attorney of Cole County, Missouri and John C. Hall and R. T. Wood vs. John L. Sullivan, Secretary of State of the State of Missouri, and Frank W. McAllister, Attorney-General of the State of Missouri, 1920; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The State of Ohio Exx Rel. Wallace D. Yaple vs. David S. Creamer, Treasurer of State, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Brief and Argument in Opposition to Petiton, 1911; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Box: 1, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Commission of Ohio vs. David Brown, 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: State vs. Newman Lumber Company, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: The People of the State of Michigan vs. Leroy Brazee, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: People of the State of Michigan, vs. Leroy Brazee, 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Progress in the New York Court of Appeals, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: The People of the State of Illinois, Defendant in Error, v. City of Chicago, Plaintiff in Error, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Northern Pacific R.R.Gco. Vs. State of Washington, 32 Sutz. Ct. 160, 1912; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: The People of the State of Michigan vs. Leroy Brazee, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: The Industrial Commission of Ohio, et al, vs. David Brown, 1913; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)